# Arezoo Alipanah

phone: +989195529919 LinkedIn: <u>arezooalipanah</u>
Email: arzalipanah@qmail.com Github: <u>arezooalipanah</u>

Website: arezooalipanah.netlify.app

I am a **software developer** with 8+ years of work experience. My passion for coding stems from the fact that it allows me to break out of the monotony of everyday life and pursue creative problem-solving. My primary goal is to design system architecture for millions of users, and to achieve this, I am always eager to learn any new technologies, concepts, or programming languages necessary. Currently, I am transitioning to Java programming and striving to master microservices patterns.

Main skills: Java, Spring, Javascript, Typescript, ReactJS

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Java Developer ~6 months 11/2020 - 12/2022

implemented the following 2 projects from scratch with Spring Boot, and connected to the services using feign client: <a href="https://doi.org/10.1007/journal.com/authentication-service">authentication-service</a>

telepardaz-service

Technologies: Spring (Boot, Data, Security-OAuth2.o, Cloud, Hibernate)

## **Kian Digital** — Senior Front Developer (Tehran Iran)

**2+** years 11/2020 - 12/2022

<u>Bourseon</u>, <u>kiandigital-blog</u>, in the Bourseon project, I implemented a lot of features and ultimately turned it into a CMS that we could quickly use to implement almost all of the company's website.

Develop **Dabi** project, a sales and consulting platform.

I've started Bourseon-data project from scratch, and its job is to crawl data related to stocks.

Technologies: Javascript, NextJS, Sanic

Contact: Mahsa Jabbari (Manager) - +989367016280

## **Maktab Sharif** — Frontend Trainer (Part time)

**~1.5** *years* 9/2022 - 12/2020

## **Tosan Techno** — Frontend Developer (Tehran Iran)

~1 *year* 10/2019 - 10/2020

<u>Seller.shopp.market</u>, started from scratch with a backend developer at Shop company, any business can easily turn into an online store with it.

Technologies: Typescript, ReactJS

Contact-linkedin: hamed-farzanefar

## **PersianGig** — Frontend Developer (Tehran Iran)

**1+** *years* 10/2018 - 7/2019

<u>Persiangig</u> is a platform for purchasing cloud infrastructure services. I implemented its custom design system from scratch.

Technologies: Typescript, ReactJS, Redux

Contact: Amir Yavand Hasani (Manager) - +989129211893

#### **Freelance** Frontend Developer

**~3** years 2015 - 2018

<u>Pedu.sharif.edu</u> <u>Codinic</u>

TamirkarsalamVakil-android-applicationDerayatacademyVakil-web-applicationes724Tozino-android-application

Technologies: Javascript, ReactJS, JQuery

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **Golestan University**, Golestan — BSc

9/2009 - 9/2013

Computer Science, Thesis: Implementation of face detection and recognition application with C#.

#### **SKILLS**

Programming Languages Java, JavaScript, TypeScript

FrameWork & Technology Spring (Boot, Data, Security-OAuth2.o, Cloud), Hibernate, Kafka, RabbitMQ

ReactJS, NextJS

DataBase MySql, MongoDB, Redis, H2

Servers Tomcat, nginx

Test Unit Testing (AssertJ, Mockito), Integration Testing (MockMVC)

Build Tools Maven, npm

DevOps & CI/CD Docker, docker-compose, Linux

## Languages

Farsi: native, English: upper intermediate